{
    "subject": "resource/Chris_Sarandon",
    "predicate": "ontology/almaMater",
    "object": "resource/West_Virginia_University",
    "human_readable": "Chris Sarandon attended West Virginia University.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9883037805557251,
            "question": "Is West Virginia University a place Chris Sarandon has attended?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9526605010032654,
            "question": "Was West Virginia University a part of Chris Sarandon's educational journey?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8898019790649414,
            "question": "Where did Chris Sarandon attend university?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8653164505958557,
            "question": "Which university is Chris Sarandon known to have attended?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8448933959007263,
            "question": "What is the name of the university Chris Sarandon attended?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7808226346969604,
            "question": "To which university did Chris Sarandon go?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7585368752479553,
            "question": "Chris Sarandon's education includes attending which university?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7124151587486267,
            "question": "What university is Chris Sarandon associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6902040839195251,
            "question": "Did Chris Sarandon go to college?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5848655104637146,
            "question": "What educational institution was Chris Sarandon a student at?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Chris Sarandon attended West Virginia University.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7947_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Did Chris Sarandon go to college?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7947_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What university is Chris Sarandon associated with?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7947_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Chris Sarandon's education includes attending which university?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7947_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7947_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7947_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7947_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7947_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7947_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7947_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7947_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7947_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7947_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7947_58.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents clearly state that Chris Sarandon earned a bachelor's degree in speech at West Virginia University, confirming the query."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}